http://haciendarustica.com/privacypolicy/

sales@haciendarustica.com
Home5 shelf rolling towerAbout Usabout usAlberta custom furnitureAngel bedArmoires by HaciendaRusticachairschestsCom6TBconsolescubboardsCustom Mahogany Vintage Single and double Doors Gary New Yorkcustom_bars.htmcustom_bedsdresser 12 drwDresser Com6Dressersend tablesgoogled6c1b1aa7ed0819e.htmlHaciendaRustica manufacturing Mexican hacienda style furniture and doors since 1946Home Page Indexhttps://haciendarustica.com/custom_entry_fabricators.htmkitchen rustic style all woodmexican carved furnituremexican dining tablesmexican doorsmexican dressersMexican dressersMexican rustic bookcasesmexican_custom_furnituremission furnishingsnightstandsoffice furnitureParis rusticsolid wood dining setPrivacy PolicyRia Atkins Bishop Ca. Modus Operandumspanish collectionSpanish revival doorsvanities
Privacy PolicyHaciendaRustica.com Terms and Conditions of Use
HaciendaRustica.com Terms and Conditions of Use1.  All orders must be in writing and sent via US mail, fax or E-mail. This last one means through our merchant PayPal, you will get a transaction confirmation within seconds and your furniture is then acknowledged. Via via email you will get a confirmation request to clarify any doubts on size,  color etc.   * For wholesaler only: If you don’t use purchase orders, HaciendaRustica.Com will assign a purchase order for future reference. We acknowledge all orders, if you do not receive an acknowledgment within 3 days, order is not being schedule for any reason you may contact us at the address and phone numbers at the foot of his page.2.  Wholesale furniture: depending on reputation, credit and location if approved all initial orders must be for a minimum of  $16,000.00 U.S.D.  contact us for confidential price list.  see # 10.You will then have access to our catalog and wholesale prices, even if you already have a Resale License we need a signed affidavit from company owner. Credit Card, Merchant Service will be available HaciendaRustica accepts these method of payment for retail and wholesale transactions (Sorry, no Paypal). You will then have access to our catalog and wholesale prices, even if you already have a Resale License we need a signed affidavit from company owner.3. All custom orders require 50% deposit with a Company check, balance to be paid with Cashier’s check made to the order of Hacienda Rustica Co. mexican rustic furniture at the confirmed shipping. We do not Ship COD (Cash on Delivery).4. For wholesale orders, all prices are FOB Mexicali or Ciudad Juarez,  Mexico subject to change without prior notification. we will respect the prices for orders that have been quoted or processed by HaciendaRustica.Com email records will suffice. Retail or public can pay with personal check or all majors cards on their initial deposit and cashiers check on delivery, or most preferably using  visa, mc, amex, or PayPal our preferred processor, for your safe shopping experience we honor all credit card.5.  Delivery is now an option at Hacienda Rustica Co. One option is  ABF freight or other freight companies are available they are not the least expensive but the best most reliable and most courteous service HaciendaRustica.Com.  In order to ensure great quality on delivery of you mexican rustic furniture. Customers must provide shipping address when order is placed to avoid production and delivery delays.  All regular orders average a delivery of 3-4 weeks from deposit/payment or last modification to your mexican furniture or delivery method approval date.5-A. Custom orders take 3-8 weeks from deposit/payment or last modification to furniture or delivery method approval date.  Customers must inspect the goods on delivery and report to the driver if you see damage on your goods and  you may request a copy of that report. Freight may represent a large percentage on small orders, reason being all our mexican furniture is already assembled, therefore bulky for shipping.  We at HaciendaRustica.Com  fine hacienda furniture has calculated the freight costs and negotiated the lowest prices for the convenience of our customers.  Also consider the savings on tax if you order is outside California and the fact that our manufactured products are of  superior quality.6. HaciendaRustica.Com is not responsible for merchandise that is lost, damaged, or delayed by any shipping company. All claims must be made to  the Freight Company within one week of receipt of goods. If packaging is damaged, please indicate this on the bill of lading or referred as BOL Original Delivery slip must be kept.  If a replacement is necessary, the furniture cannot be of different dimensions then the original shipment, reason being some customers order without understanding furniture dimensions.7. Privacy Policy:***ADDED ON FEB. 2 2006 DO NOT LET DELIVERY DRIVER LEAVE WITHOUT INSPECTING CONTENTS ON ALL BOXES***The style of the furniture is RUSTIC, therefore, it is subject to irregularities due to the handcrafted process. Color and dimensions may change slightly. Normal cracking adds to the furniture handcrafted beauty and uniqueness of the piece, so it may not be considered a reason for return.8. Any cancellation must be made in writing within one week of acknowledgment. If merchandise has been shipped, customer must pay for freight plus 15% restocking fee.9. HaciendaRustica.Com reserves the right to cancel items that are no longer available. Orders for discontinued items will not be accepted, even though we have not discontinued any items since 1995. EXCEPT SOME ITEMS NO LONGER DISPLAYED ON THE CARVED AND PAINTED LINE ON JUNE 2000.10. All returns or local repairs are accepted without prior written authorization. All replacements required to have a new purchase order issued. In order to supply consistent quality on mexican hacienda furniture manufactured by Hacienda Rustica factory We are not opening new wholesale accounts as of October 2001 until further notice! We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone.11. Any court disputes or legal issues, concerns which require court appearance will occur in the jurisdiction of the vendor, in the City of Los Angeles, California.Privacy PolicyThank You Oscar Almaguer HaciendaRustica.Com
Hacienda Rustica.com Privacy Policy PDF
Google+
